Elmo Roper Papers
© 2002 University of Connecticut
- Series I: Correspondence, undated, 1909-1972
  - Subseries C: Professional, undated, 1940-1972
    - Election, 1948
      - T - Wa, 1948 (Box 5:307)
      - Wa - Wi, 1948 (Box 5:308)
    - American Weekly, 1949 (Box 6:309)
    - Aa - Al, 1949 (Box 6:310)
    - Am - Ar, 1949 (Box 6:311)
    - Atlantic Union Committee
      - Finances, January - May, 1949 (Box 6:312)
      - Finances, June - December, 1949 (Box 6:313)
      - January - February, 1949 (Box 6:314)
      - March, 1949 (Box 6:315)
      - April, 1949 (Box 6:316)
      - May, 1949 (Box 6:317)
      - June, 1949 (Box 6:318)
      - July - August, 1949 (Box 6:319)
      - September - October, 1949 (Box 6:320)
      - November - December, 1949 (Box 6:321)
    - Atlantic Union Committee/World Federalists
      - April - June, 1949 (Box 6:322)
      - July, 1949 (Box 6:323)
      - August - December, 1949 (Box 6:324)
    - Ba, 1949 (Box 6:325)
    - Be, 1949 (Box 6:326)
    - Bi - Br, 1949 (Box 6:327)
    - Bu, 1949 (Box 6:328)
    - Baxter, James, 1949 (Box 6:329)
    - B'nai B'rith, 1949 (Box 6:330)
    - Bowles, Chester, 1949 (Box 6:331)
    - Ca - Ch, 1949 (Box 6:332)
    - Cl - Col, 1949 (Box 6:333)
    - Con - Cow, 1949 (Box 6:334)
    - D, 1949 (Box 6:335)
    - Ec - Ed, 1949 (Box 6:336)
    - El - Ev, 1949 (Box 6:337)
    - Election, 1949 (Box 6:338-339)
    - Election materials, 1949 (Box 6:340)
    - Fa - Fe, 1949 (Box 6:341)
    - Fi - Fu, 1949 (Box 6:342)
    - Ford Motor Company, 1949 (Box 6:343)
    - G - Ha, 1949 (Box 6:344)
    - Ho - Hu, 1949 (Box 6:345)
    - I, 1949 (Box 6:346)
    - J - L, 1949 (Box 6:347)
    - Middletowns, Inc., 1949 (Box 6:348)
    - M, 1949 (Box 6:349)
    - Magazine Audience Group, 1949 (Box 6:350)
    - N - O, 1949 (Box 6:351)
    - P - R, 1949 (Box 6:352)
    - S, 1949 (Box 6:353)
    - T, 1949 (Box 6:354)
    - W, 1949 (Box 6:355)
    - A, 1950 (Box 6:356)
    - Atlantic Union Committee
      - February - March, 1950 (Box 6:357)
      - April - August, 1950 (Box 6:358)
      - September - November, 1950 (Box 6:359)
      - Background, 1950 (Box 6:360)
    - Advertising Motivation Survey (Project X)
      - January - March, 1950 (Box 6:361)
      - March, 1950 (Box 6:362)
      - April, 1950 (Box 6:363)
      - May, 1950 (Box 6:364)
      - June - November, 1950 (Box 6:365)
      - December, 1950 (Box 6:366)
      - Background, 1950 (Box 6:367)
    - B, 1950 (Box 7:368)
    - Leo Burnett Company, Inc., 1950 (Box 7:369)
    - C, 1950 (Box 7:370)
    - Connecticut Interracial Commission, January - February, 1950 (Box 7:371)
    - Connecticut Interracial Commission, March - November, 1950 (Box 7:372)
    - D - G, 1950 (Box 7:373)
    - Ford Motor Company, February - August, 1950 (Box 7:374)
    - Ford Motor Company, September - November, 1950 (Box 7:375)
    - Election, 1950 (Box 7:376)
    - Ha - Ho, 1950 (Box 7:377)
    - Hodgins, Eric, January - September, 1950 (Box 7:378)
    - Hodgins, Eric, October - December, 1950 (Box 7:379)
    - S. C. Johnson & Son, Inc., 1950 (Box 7:380)
    - J - L, 1950 (Box 7:381)
    - Ma, 1950 (Box 7:382)
    - Mc - Mu, 1950 (Box 7:383)
    - Manheimer Anti-Semitism Survey, 1950 (Box 7:384-385)
    - Manheimer Anti-Semitism Survey, Background, 1950 (Box 7:386)
    - McMahon, Brien, 1950 (Box 7:387)
    - Mental Health Survey, 1950 (Box 7:388)
    - Na - Nat, 1950 (Box 7:389)
    - Nat - Ni, 1950 (Box 7:390)
    - O - Pa, 1950 (Box 7:391)
    - Pe - Pr, 1950 (Box 7:392)
    - Ra - Roo, 1950 (Box 7:393)
    - Rop - Ru, 1950 (Box 7:394)
    - S, 1950 (Box OS)
    - Sa - St, 1950 (Box 7:396)
    - Speeches, 1950 (Box 7:397)
    - T - U, 1950 (Box 7:398)
    - Urban League, January - August, 1950 (Box 7:399)
    - Urban League, September - November, 1950 (Box 7:400)
    - W, 1950 (Box 7:401)
    - A, 1951 (Box 7:402)
    - Atlantic Union Committee
      - March - June, 1951 (Box 7:403)
      - July - September, 1951 (Box 7:404)
      - October - November, 1951 (Box 7:405)
      - December, 1951 (Box 7:406)
    - B, 1951 (Box 7:407)
    - C, 1951 (Box 7:408)
    - CBS-TV script, 1951 (Box 7:409)
    - D - F, 1951 (Box 7:410)
    - Ford Motor Company, 1951 (Box 7:411)
    - G - H, 1951 (Box 7:412)
    - I - L, 1951 (Box 7:413)
    - Ma - Mc, 1951 (Box 7:414)
    - Me - Mo, 1951 (Box 7:415)
    - Mental Health, 1951 (Box 7:416)
    - N, 1951 (Box 7:417)
    - National Planning Association, 1951 (Box 7:418)
    - O - P, 1951 (Box 7:419)
    - R, 1951 (Box 7:420)
    - Se - Sp, 1951 (Box 7:421)
    - St - T, 1951 (Box 7:422)
    - Speeches, 1951 (Box 7:423)
    - Urban League, February - June, 1951 (Box 8:424)
    - Urban League, August - November, 1951 (Box 8:425)
    - Wa, 1951 (Box 8:426)
    - We - Y, 1951 (Box 8:427)
    - A, 1952 (Box 8:428)
    - Atlantic Union Committee
      - January - February, 1952 (Box 8:429)
      - March - April, 1952 (Box 8:430)
      - May - June, 1952 (Box 8:431)
      - July - August, 1952 (Box 8:432)
      - September - October, 1952 (Box 8:433)
      - November, 1952 (Box 8:434)
      - November - December, 1952 (Box 8:435)
    - B - Be, 1952 (Box 8:436)
    - Bo - Bu, 1952 (Box 8:437)
    - C - D, 1952 (Box 8:438)
    - E - F, 1952 (Box 8:439)
    - Election, 1952 (Box 8:440-442)
    - Fund for the Republic, 1952 (Box 8:443)
    - G - He, 1952 (Box 8:444)
    - Ho - Hu, 1952 (Box 8:445)
    - I - L, 1952 (Box 8:446)
    - M - P, 1952 (Box 8:447)
    - NBC, January - March, 1952 (Box 8:448)
    - NBC, June - November, 1952 (Box 8:449)
    - N - P, 1952 (Box 8:450)
    - National Planning Association, March - April, 1952 (Box 8:451)
    - National Planning Association, July - December, 1952 (Box 8:452)
    - R, 1952 (Box 8:453)
    - Roper, 1952 (Box 8:454)
    - Sa - Sh, 1952 (Box 8:456)
    - Si, 1952 (Box 8:457-458)
    - So - Sw, 1952 (Box 8:459)
    - Speeches, 1952 (Box 8:460)
    - T - U, 1952 (Box 8:461)
    - Wa - We, 1952 (Box 8:462)
    - Wh - Wo, 1952 (Box 8:463)
    - Wo - Wy, 1952 (Box 8:464)
    - A, 1953 (Box 8:465)
    - B, 1953 (Box 8:466)
    - Atlantic Union Committee
      - January - March, 1953 (Box 8:467)
      - April - May, 1953 (Box 8:468)
      - June - November, 1953 (Box 8:469)
    - Connecticut Commission on Civil Rights, 1953 (Box 8:470)
    - C, 1953 (Box 8:471)
    - Connecticut Commission to Study the Potentials of the Aging, 1953 (Box 8:472)
    - D, 1953 (Box 8:473)
    - F, 1953 (Box 8:474)
    - Franklin D. Roosevelt Foundation, 1953 (Box 8:475)
    - Fund for the Republic
      - January - March, 1953 (Box 8:476)
      - April - May, 1953 (Box 8:477)
      - June - July, 1953 (Box 8:478)
      - August - September, 1953 (Box 8:479)
      - October - November, 1953 (Box 8:480)
    - G - H, 1953 (Box 8:481)
    - Hodgins, Eric, 1953 (Box 8:482)
    - I - L, 1953 (Box 8:483)
    - M, 1953 (Box 8:484)
    - N, 1953 (Box 8:485)
    - P, 1953 (Box 8:486)
    - Purdue Communication Study, 1953 (Box 8:487)
    - R, 1953 (Box 8:488)
    - Roper Employee Attitude Survey, 1953 (Box 8:489)
    - Sa - Sm, 1953 (Box 8:491)
    - So - St, 1953 (Box 8:492)
    - San Francisco Bay Area Council, 1953 (Box 9:493)
    - Speeches, 1953 (Box 9:494)
    - T - U, 1953 (Box 9:495)
    - Wa - Wo, 1953 (Box 9:496)
    - A, 1954 (Box 9:497)
    - Atlantic Union Committee, 1954 (Box 9:498)
    - Ba - Bo, 1954 (Box 9:499)
    - Br - Bu, 1954 (Box 9:500)
    - C, 1954 (Box 9:501)
    - D - F, 1954 (Box 9:502)
    - Fund for the Republic
      - March - May, 1954 (Box 9:503)
      - June - August, 1954 (Box 9:504)
      - September - December, 1954 (Box 9:505)
    - H, 1954 (Box 9:506)
    - I - M, 1954 (Box 9:507)
    - N - P, 1954 (Box 9:508)
    - R, 1954 (Box 9:509)
    - Sa - Sp, 1954 (Box 9:510)
    - St, 1954 (Box 9:511)
    - Speeches, 1954 (Box 9:512)
    - T - V, 1954 (Box 9:513)
    - Umpawaug Company, 1954 (Box 9:514)
    - W, 1954 (Box 9:515)
    - A, 1955 (Box 9:517)
    - American Association for Public Opinion Research (AAPOR), 1955 (Box 9:518)
    - Atlantic Union Committee
      - January, 1955 (Box 9:519)
      - February - June, 1955 (Box 9:520)
      - July, 1955 (Box 9:521)
      - August - Spetember, 1955 (Box 9:522)
      - November, 1955 (Box 9:523)
      - December, 1955 (Box 9:524)
    - Audits and Surveys, January - August, 1955 (Box 9:525)
    - Audits and Surveys, September - December, 1955 (Box 9:526)
    - B, 1955 (Box 9:527)
    - C, 1955 (Box 9:528)
    - D, 1955 (Box 9:529)
    - E - F, 1955 (Box 9:530)
    - Fund for the Republic
      - March - September, 1955 (Box 9:531)
      - October, 1955 (Box 9:532)
      - November, 1955 (Box 9:533-534)
      - December, 1955 (Box 9:535-536)
    - H, 1955 (Box 9:537)
    - I - K, 1955 (Box 9:538)
    - L, 1955 (Box 9:539)
    - M, 1955 (Box 9:540)
    - N - O, 1955 (Box 9:541)
    - National Planning Association, 1955 (Box 9:542)
    - P - R, 1955 (Box 9:543)
    - Roper [business], 1955 (Box 9:544)
    - Sa - Sp, 1955 (Box 9:545)
    - Sp - St, 1955 (Box 9:546)
    - T - U, 1955 (Box 9:547)
    - Umpawaug Company, 1955 (Box 9:548)
    - W, 1955 (Box 9:549)
    - Atlantic Union Committee
      - January, 1956 (Box 9:550)
      - February - April, 1956 (Box 9:551)
      - May, 1956 (Box 9:552)
      - June, 1956 (Box 10:553)
      - July, 1956 (Box 10:554)
      - August - September, 1956 (Box 10:555)
      - November - December, 1956 (Box 10:556)
      - Publications, 1956 (Box 10:557)
    - Audits and Surveys, 1956 (Box 10:558)
    - Fund for the Republic
      - January, 1956 (Box 10:559-560)
      - February, 1956 (Box 10:561-562)
      - March - May, 1956 (Box 10:563)
      - June, 1956 (Box 10:564)
      - July, 1956 (Box 10:565)
      - August, 1956 (Box 10:566)
      - September, 1956 (Box 10:567)
      - October, 1956 (Box 10:568)
      - November, 1956 (Box 10:569)
      - December, 1956 (Box 10:570)
      - Congratulations, November, 1956 (Box 10:571)
      - Congratulations, November - December, 1956 (Box 10:572)
    - F - I, 1956 (Box 10:573)
    - M - U, 1956 (Box 10:574)
    - A - Am, 1957 (Box 10:575)
    - Am - As, 1957 (Box 10:576)
    - Atlantic Union Committee
      - January, 1957 (Box 10:577)
      - February, 1957 (Box 10:578)
      - March - April, 1957 (Box 10:579)
      - May, 1957 (Box 10:580)
      - June, 1957 (Box 10:581)
      - July, 1957 (Box 10:582)
      - August, 1957 (Box 10:583)
      - September, 1957 (Box 10:584)
      - October, 1957 (Box 10:585)
      - November - December, 1957 (Box 10:586)
    - Atlantic Union Committee--A Declaration of Interpendence, 1957
      - November, 1957 (Box 10:587-588)
      - December, 1957 (Box 10:589-593)
    - Audits and Surveys, 1957 (Box 10:594)
    - B, 1957 (Box 10:595)
    - C - E, 1957 (Box 10:596)
    - Democratic Senatorial Campaign Committee, 1957 (Box 10:597)
    - Empire Trust Company, 1957 (Box 10:598)
    - F, 1957 (Box 10:599)
    - Fund for the Republic
      - January - February, 1957 (Box 10:600)
      - February, 1957 (Box 10:601)
      - March, 1957 (Box 10:602-603)
      - April, 1957 (Box 10:604-605)
      - May, 1957 (Box 10:606-608)
      - June, 1957 (Box 11:609-611)
      - July, 1957 (Box 11:612-615)
      - August, 1957 (Box 11:616-620)
      - September, 1957 (Box 11:621-624)
      - October, 1957 (Box 11:625-628)
      - November, 1957 (Box 11:629-630)
      - December, 1957 (Box 11:631-632)
    - Fund for the Republic--American Traditions Dinner
      - January - February, 1957 (Box 11:633)
      - February, 1957 (Box 11:634)
    - Fund for the Republic
      - Confidential, 1957 (Box 11:635)
    - G, 1957 (Box 11636:)
    - H, 1957 (Box 11:637)
    - Hodgins, Eric, 1957 (Box 11:638)
    - Home Life Insurance Company, 1957 (Box 11:639)
    - I - J, 1957 (Box 11:640)
    - K - L, 1957 (Box 11:641)
    - M, 1957 (Box 11:642)
    - McCann-Erickson, 1957 (Box 11:643)
    - Na - Ne, 1957 (Box 11:644)
    - Ne - Ni, 1957 (Box 11:645)
    - O - P, 1957 (Box 11:646)
    - Phillip Morris, 1957 (Box 11:647)
    - Phillip Morris--Marlboro Survey, 1957 (Box 11:648)
    - R, 1957 (Box 11:649)
    - Sh - Sp, 1957 (Box 11:651)
    - St, 1957 (Box 11:652)
    - Saturday Review, 1957 (Box 11:653)
    - T - V, 1957 (Box 11:654)
    - Umpawaug Company, 1957 (Box 11:655)
    - W, 1957 (Box 11:656)
    - A, 1958 (Box 11:658)
    - American Association for Public Opinion Research (AAPOR), 1958 (Box 11:)
    - Arkansas Gazette, March - June, 1958 (Box 11:660)
    - Arkansas Gazette, August - November, 1958 (Box 11:661)
    - Atlantic Union Committee
      - January, 1958 (Box 12:662)
      - February - March, 1958 (Box 12:663)
      - April, 1958 (Box 12:664)
      - May - June, 1958 (Box 12:665)
      - July, 1958 (Box 12:666)
      - August - September, 1958 (Box 12:667)
      - October, 1958 (Box 12:668)
      - November December, 1958 (Box 12:669)
    - Atlantic Union Committee--A Declaration of Interdependence, 1958 (Box 12:670)
    - B, 1958 (Box 12:671)
    - Benton, William, January - May, 1958 (Box 12:672)
    - Benton, William, October - December, 1958 (Box 12:673)
    - Ca - Ch, 1958 (Box 12:674)
    - Co - Cr, 1958 (Box 12:675)
    - Da - De, 1958 (Box 12:676)
    - Di - Du, 1958 (Box 12:677)
    - E - Fl, 1958 (Box 12:678)
    - Fo - Fu, 1958 (Box 12:679)
    - Fjeld, E. I., 1958 (Box 12:680)
    - Fund for the Republic
      - January, 1958 (Box 12:681)
      - February, 1958 (Box 12:682)
      - March, 1958 (Box 12:683)
      - April, 1958 (Box 12:684-685)
      - May, 1958 (Box 12:686)
      - June, 1958 (Box 12:687)
      - July, 1958 (Box 12:688)
      - July - August, 1958 (Box 12:689)
      - September, 1958 (Box 12:690)
      - October, 1958 (Box 12:691)
      - November, 1958 (Box 12:692)
      - December, 1958 (Box 12:693)
    - G, 1958 (Box 12:694)
    - H, 1958 (Box 12:695)
    - Hodgins, Eric, Public Pulse, 1958 (Box 12:696)
    - I - K, 1958 (Box 12:697)
    - L - Me, 1958 (Box 12:698)
    - Mi - Mu, 1958 (Box 12:699)
    - N, 1958 (Box 12:700)
    - National Newspaper Syndicate, March - July, 1958 (Box 12:701)
    - National Newspaper Syndicate, August - December, 1958 (Box 12:702)
    - National Planning Association, 1958 (Box 12:703)
    - O, 1958 (Box 12:704)
    - P, 1958 (Box 12:705)
    - Pineapple Growers' Association of Hawaii, 1958 (Box 12:706)
    - Public Pulse, March - May, 1958 (Box 12:707)
    - Public Pulse, June - October, 1958 (Box 12:708)
    - Q - R, 1958 (Box 12:709)
    - Roper [business/personal], 1958 (Box 12:710)
    - Roper [business], 1958 (Box 13:723)
    - Sa - So, 1958 (Box 13:728)
    - Sp - St, 1958 (Box 13:729)
    - Steichen, Edward (Colonel), 1958 (Box 13:730)
    - Speeches, January - May, 1958 (Box 13:731)
    - Speeches, June - November, 1958 (Box 13:732)
    - T - U, 1958 (Box 13:733)
    - Umpawaug Company, 1958 (Box 13:734)
    - V, 1958 (Box 13:735)
    - W - Wi, 1958 (Box 13:736)
    - Wo - Z, 1958 (Box 13:737)
    - Williams College
      - January - February, 1958 (Box 13:738)
      - March, 1958 (Box 13:739)
      - April - June, 1958 (Box 13:740)
      - July - October, 1958 (Box 13:741)
      - November - December, no month indicated, 1958 (Box 13:742)
    - Wyatt, Wilson, October - November, 1958 (Box 13:743)
    - Wyatt, Wilson, November - December, 1958 (Box 13:744)
    - Ab - Ag, 1959 (Box 13:745)
    - Ar - Am, 1959 (Box 13:746)
    - Am - An, 1959 (Box 13:747)
    - An - Au, 1959 (Box 13:748)
    - Advertising Council, 1959 (Box 13:749)
    - Atlantic Union Committee
      - January, 1959 (Box 13:750)
      - February - March, 1959 (Box 13:751)
      - April, 1959 (Box 13:752)
      - May, 1959 (Box 13:753)
      - June - July, 1959 (Box 13:754)
      - August - September, 1959 (Box 13:755)
      - October - November, 1959 (Box 13:756)
      - December, 1959 (Box 13:757)
    - Atlantic Union Committee-NATO Conference
      - June - December, 1958 (Box 13:758)
      - December, 1958 (Box 13:759)
      - January - March, 1959 (Box 13:760)
      - March - April, 1959 (Box 13:761)
      - May, 1959 (Box 13:762)
      - June, 1959 (Box 13:763-764)
      - July - August, 1959 (Box 13:765)
      - September, 1959 (Box 13:766)
    - Audits and Surveys, January - March, 1959 (Box 13:767)
    - Audits and Surveys, April - December, 1959 (Box 13:768)
    - Ba, 1959 (Box 13:769)
    - Be - Bl, 1959 (Box 13:770)
    - Bo - Bu, 1959 (Box 13:771)
    - Ca - Cha, 1959 (Box 14:772)
    - Chi - Cu, 1959 (Box 14:773)
    - CBS, 1959 (Box 14:774)
    - Connecticut Commission on Civil Rights, April - October, 1959 (Box 14:775)
    - Connecticut Commission on Civil Rights, November - December, 1959 (Box 14:776)
    - Da - De, 1959 (Box 14:777)
    - Di - Du, 1959 (Box 14:778)
    - E, 1959 (Box 14:779)
    - Fa - Fi, 1959 (Box 14:780)
    - Fl - Fo, 1959 (Box 14:781)
    - Fo - Fu, 1959 (Box 14:782)
    - Fund for the Republic
      - January, 1959 (Box 14:783)
      - February, 1959 (Box 14:784)
      - March - April, 1959 (Box 14:785)
      - June - July, 1959 (Box 14:786)
      - August - October, 1959 (Box 14:787)
      - October - December, 1959 (Box 14:788)
    - Ga - Go, 1959 (Box 14:789)
    - Gr - Gu, 1959 (Box 14:790)
    - Ha - Hi, 1959 (Box 14:791)
    - Ho - Hu, 1959 (Box 14:792)
    - Hawkins, William E., Jr., March - August, 1959 (Box 14:793)
    - Hawkins, William E., Jr., September - December, 1959 (Box 14:794)
    - I, 1959 (Box 14:795)
    - J, 1959 (Box 14:796)
    - Ka - Ko, 1959 (Box 14:797)
    - Kr - Ku, 1959 (Box 14:798)
    - La, 1959 (Box 14:799)
    - La - Lu, 1959 (Box 14:800)
    - Ma, 1959 (Box 14:801)
    - Mc - Mi, 1959 (Box 14:802)
    - Mo, 1959 (Box 14:803)
    - Mo - Mu, 1959 (Box 14:804)
    - Na, 1959 (Box 14:805)
    - Na - Ne, 1959 (Box 14:806)
    - Ne - Ni, 1959 (Box 14:807)
    - National Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy, 1959 (Box 14:808)
    - National Planning Association, 1959 (Box 14:809)
    - O, 1959 (Box 14:810)
    - Pa - Pi, 1959 (Box 14:811)
    - Po - Q, 1959 (Box 14:812)
    - Public Pulse, 1959 (Box 14:813)
    - Ra - Re, 1959 (Box 14:814)
    - Re - Ru, 1959 (Box 14:815)
    - Roper [business], 1959 (Box 14:816)
    - Roper Center, January - May, 1959 (Box 14:817)
    - Roper Center, June - October, 1959 (Box 14:818)
    - Roper Center, November - December, 1959 (Box 14:819)
    - Sc - Si, 1959 (Box 14:830)
    - Sn - So, 1959 (Box 14:831)
    - Sp - St, 1959 (Box 14:832)
    - St - Sw, 1959 (Box 15:833)
    - Saturday Review, 1959 (Box OS)
    - Saturday Review, April - July, 1959 (Box 15:834)
    - Saturday Review, September - December, 1959 (Box 15:835)
    - Speeches, January - March, 1959 (Box 15:836)
    - Speeches, March - April, 1959 (Box 15:837)
    - Speeches, July - September, 1959 (Box 15:838)
    - Te - Ti, 1959 (Box 15:839)
    - Ti - Tr, 1959 (Box 15:840)
    - Ul - Un, 1959 (Box 15:841)
    - Un - V, 1959 (Box 15:842)
    - Umpawaug Company, 1959 (Box 15:843)
    - Umpawaug Company, 1959 (Box OS)
    - Wa - Wi, 1959 (Box 15:844)
    - Wo - Y, 1959 (Box 15:845)
    - Wyatt, Wilson, 1959 (Box 15:846)
    - A - Am, 1960 (Box 15:847)
    - Am, 1960 (Box 15:848)
    - Am - As, 1960 (Box 15:849)
    - Advertising Council, February - April, 1960 (Box 15:850)
    - Advertising Council, June - August, 1960 (Box 15:851)
    - Atlantic Union Committee
      - January, 1960 (Box 15:852)
      - January - February, 1960 (Box 15:853)
      - February, 1960 (Box 15:854)
      - March - April, 1960 (Box 15:855)
      - May, 1960 (Box 15:856-857)
      - June, 1960 (Box 15:858-860)
      - July, 1960 (Box 15:861)
      - August, 1960 (Box 15:862-863)
      - September, 1960 (Box 15:864-865)
      - October, 1960 (Box 15:866)
      - November - December, 1960 (Box 15:867)
      - December, 1960 (Box 15:868-869)
    - B - Be, 1960 (Box 15:870)
    - Bi - Bo, 1960 (Box 15:871)
    - Bo - Br, 1960 (Box 15:872)
    - Bu - By, 1960 (Box 15:873)
    - C - Ce, 1960 (Box 15:874)
    - Ch - Cl, 1960 (Box 15:875)
    - Co, 1960 (Box 15:876)
    - Co - Cr, 1960 (Box 15:877)
    - Case, Clifford P., 1960 (Box 15:878)
    - CBS
      - February - April, 1960 (Box 15:879)
      - April, 1960 (Box 15:880)
      - May, 1960 (Box 15:881)
      - June - September, 1960 (Box 15:882)
      - October, 1960 (Box 15:883-884)
      - November, 1960 (Box 15:885)
    - Connecticut Commission on Civil Rights
      - Correspondence, 1960 (Box 15:886)
      - Publications, 1960 (Box 15:887-888)
    - D, 1960 (Box 15:889)
    - E, 1960 (Box 15:890)
    - Election
      - January - May, 1960 (Box 15:891)
      - June, 1960 (Box 15:892-893)
      - June - July, 1960 (Box 15:894)
      - August - October, 1960 (Box 15:895)
      - November, 1960 (Box 15:896)
    - Fa - Fi, 1960 (Box 16:897)
    - Fi - Fl, 1960 (Box 16:898)
    - Fo, 1960 (Box 16:899)
    - Fr - Fu, 1960 (Box 16:900)
    - Fund for the Republic
      - January - February, 1960 (Box 16:901)
      - March, 1960 (Box 16:902)
      - April - August, 1960 (Box 16:903)
      - August, 1960 (Box 16:904)
      - September, 1960 (Box 16:905)
      - October - December, 1960 (Box 16:906)
    - Ga - Go, 1960 (Box 16:907)
    - Gr - Gu, 1960 (Box 16:908)
    - Gore, Albert, 1960 (Box 16:909)
    - Griswold, Erwin N., 1960 (Box 16:910)
    - Ha, 1960 (Box 16:911-912)
    - Ha - He, 1960 (Box 16:913)
    - He - Ho, 1960 (Box 16:914)
    - Ho - Hu, 1960 (Box 16:915)
    - Home Life Insurance Cmpany, 1960 (Box 16:916)
    - Humphrey, Hubert H., 1960 (Box 16:917)
    - Il - In, 1960 (Box 16:918)
    - In - Ir, 1960 (Box 16:919)
    - International Research Associates, Inc. (INRA), 1960 (Box 16:920)
    - J - Ke, 1960 (Box 16:921)
    - Ke - Kr, 1960 (Box 16:922)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1960 (Box 16:923)
    - Kefauver, Estes, 1960 (Box 16:924)
    - Kutrz, Howard G., 1960 (Box 16:925)
    - L - Le, 1960 (Box 16:926)
    - Le, 1960 (Box 16:927)
    - Li - Lu, 1960 (Box 16:928)
    - Ma, 1960 (Box 16:929)
    - Mc - Me, 1960 (Box 16:930)
    - Mi - Mo, 1960 (Box 16:931)
    - Mo - Mu, 1960 (Box 16:932)
    - Na, 1960 (Box 16:933)
    - Na - Ne, 1960 (Box 16:934)
    - Ne, 1960 (Box 16:935)
    - Ne - No, 1960 (Box 16:936)
    - Oc - Og, 1960 (Box 16:937)
    - On - Os, 1960 (Box 16:938)
    - Pa - Pf, 1960 (Box 16:939)
    - Pi - Po, 1960 (Box 16:940)
    - Po - Q, 1960 (Box 16:941)
    - R, 1960 (Box OS)
    - Re, 1960 (Box 16:942)
    - Re - Ru, 1960 (Box 16:943)
    - Roper [business], 1960 (Box 16:944)
    - Sa - Se, 1960 (Box 16:949)
    - Sh - Sm, 1960 (Box 16:950)
    - Sp - St, 1960 (Box 16:951)
    - St, 1960 (Box 16:952-953)
    - Saturday Review, April - September, 1960 (Box 16:954)
    - Saturday Review, October - November, 1960 (Box 16:955)
    - Speeches, January - February, 1960 (Box 16:956)
    - Speeches, February - March, 1960 (Box 16:957)
    - Speeches, May - August, 1960 (Box 16:958)
    - Speeches, August - December, 1960 (Box 16:959)
    - Spiegel, Inc.
      - January - February, 1960 (Box 16:960)
      - March - December, 1960 (Box 16:961)
    - Te, 1960 (Box 16:962)
    - Th - To, 1960 (Box 16:963)
    - U, 1960 (Box 16:964)
    - Umpawaug Company, 1960 (Box 16:965)
    - Urban League, 1960 (Box 17:966)
    - V, 1960 (Box 17:967)
    - Wh - Wi, 1960 (Box 17:968)
    - Williams College
      - January - June, 1960 (Box 17:969)
      - August, 1960 (Box 17:970)
      - August - October, 1960 (Box 17:971)
      - October - December, 1960 (Box 17:972)
    - Wa -We, 1960 (Box 17:973)
    - Wi - Wy, 1960 (Box 17:974)
    - Y, 1960 (Box 17:975)
    - Ad - Am, 1961 (Box 17:981)
    - Am, 1961 (Box 17:982-983)
    - An - As, 1961 (Box 17:984)
    - Advertising Council, March - April, 1961 (Box 17:985)
    - Advertising Council, April - December, 1961 (Box 17:986)
    - Atlantic Union Committee
      - January, 1961 (Box 17:987)
      - January - February, 1961 (Box 17:988)
      - February, 1961 (Box 17:989)
      - March - April, 1961 (Box 17:990)
      - May - June, 1961 (Box 17:991)